{
  "header.menu.home": "HOME",
  "header.menu.kuniverse": "KUN AGÜERO",
  "header.menu.myavatars": "AVATARS",
  "header.menu.mint.your.avatar": "MINT YOUR AVATAR",
  "page.home.video.title": "KUN AGÜERO ENTERS THE METAVERSE",
  "page.home.video.avatars": "9320 AVATARS",
  "page.home.video.messageone": "Kun Agüero enters The Sandbox to find the best players in the Metaverse.",
  "page.home.video.messagetwo": "Mint your own avatar and become part of his team!",
  "page.home.video.mint.buttom": "Mint now",
  "page.home.play.like.a.kun.title": "PLAY LIKE KUN",
  "page.home.play.like.a.kun.text": "The Kuniverse Avatars are a collection of 9320 unique and randomly generated metaverse avatars for The Sandbox. Each one will be playable inside The Sandbox unlocking unique functionalities and giving owners the possibility to win special prizes and experiences  alongside Kun Agüero. No two avatars are the same, and each will represent the highlights of Kun’s career from football, gaming and victories throughout the years.",
  "page.home.enter.universe.title": "ENTER THE KUNIVERSE",
  "page.home.enter.universe.text": "Each avatar will be playable inside The Sandbox Metaverse, starting with the upcoming Kuniverse season  opening. Jump into the game and become a legend.",
  "page.home.lets.play.title": "VAMOS A JUGAR!",
  "page.home.lets.play.description": "By minting your Kuniverse Avatar  you will receive:",
  "page.home.lets.play.list.one": "A one of a kind playable avatar to wear in The Sandbox",
  "page.home.lets.play.list.two": "VIP access to exclusive social media channels to interact directly with Kun Agüero",
  "page.home.lets.play.list.three": "A chance to compete in exclusive challenges within the Kuniverse and win special rewards including NFT drops, merchandising and more.",
  "page.home.lets.play.list.four": "Entry to private events with Kun Agüero and other celebrities.",
  "page.home.faq.title": "F.A.Q.",
  "page.home.faq.0.question": "HOW MANY KUNIVERSE AVATARS ARE THERE?",
  "page.home.faq.0.answer": "There are a total of 9320 Kuniverse Avatars that will be minted.",
  "page.home.faq.1.question": "WHAT IS THEIR RARITY/TIER?",
  "page.home.faq.1.answer": "The avatars are divided into a variety or rarity categories depending on traits. Each avatar will be unique, and generated through a random weight of traits which affect the visual look & feel. In addition there will be multiple specially designed 1/1 NFTs.",
  "page.home.faq.2.question": "WHERE DO I HAVE TO GO CLAIM THE AVATARS?",
  "page.home.faq.2.answer": "There is only one place where you can mint the Avatars: <a href=\"https://kuniverse.sandbox.game\">https://kuniverse.sandbox.game</a>",
  "page.home.faq.3.question": "AT WHAT TIME DOES THE SALE START?",
  "page.home.faq.3.answer": "Whitelist access will begin on November 1st at 2pm UTC, 48 hours before the public sale, which starts on November 3rd, 2022, 2pm UTC.",
  "page.home.faq.4.question": "HOW MUCH SHOULD I EXPECT TO PAY FOR ONE KUNIVERSE  AVATAR NFT?",
  "page.home.faq.4.answer": "One Avatar NFT will cost 100 SAND tokens (Ethereum network).",
  "page.home.faq.5.question": "HOW MANY AVATARS CAN I MINT PER WALLET ADDRESS?",
  "page.home.faq.5.answer": "<p>The Kuniverse Avatars will be released in 2 waves:</p><ul class=\"list-decimal\"><li>November 1st, 2022, 2pm UTC : Whitelisted people of Aguero’s community and holders of previous The Sandbox Avatar Collections and LAND will have a chance to mint up to 4 avatars per wallet, within a 48 hours time frame.</li><li>November 3rd, 2022, 2pm UTC : Public release. Every user will have the chance to mint up to 10 avatars per wallet.</li></ul><p>November 4st, 2022, 2pm UTC: Reveal of the avatars on OpenSea.</p>",
  "page.home.faq.6.question": "HOW CAN I SEE MY AVATAR?",
  "page.home.faq.6.answer": "The Kun Aguero Avatars will be revealed November 4th, 2022 on OpenSea.",
  "page.home.faq.7.question": "CAN I MINT USING ANY WALLET?",
  "page.home.faq.7.answer": "Users can connect to mint with Metamask Wallet, Coinbase Wallet, and every wallet available through WalletConnect.",
  "page.home.faq.8.question": "WHAT CAN I DO WITH THE KUNIVERSE AVATARS?",
  "page.home.faq.8.answer": "<p>Each Kuniverse Avatar will be playable inside The Sandbox in all the single player and multiplayer experiences to come starting from the Kuniverse Season in November. By minting Kun Agüero's first NFT Avatar Collection you will receive:</p> <ul class=\"list-disc\"> <li>A one of a kind playable avatar to wear in The Sandbox Play-to-Earn activities for avatar holders. </li> <li>VIP access to exclusive social media channels to interact directly with Kun Agüero</li> <li>A chance to compete in exclusive challenges within the Kuniverse and win special rewards including NFT drops, merchandising and more.</li> <li>Entry to private events with Kun Agüero and other celebrities.</li> </ul>",
  "page.home.faq.9.question": "HOW CAN I USE MY AVATAR INSIDE THE SANDBOX?",
  "page.home.faq.9.answer": "You will be able to use it as an Avatar by simply selecting it in the Avatar Manager in The Sandbox dashboard once it has been enabled.",
  "page.home.faq.10.question": "WHERE CAN I BUY A KUNIVERSE AVATAR AFTER THE INITIAL SALE IS OVER?",
  "page.home.faq.10.answer": "After the initial sale is over, you will be able to purchase as many avatars as you like from users that are willing to sell theirs on the secondary marketplace OpenSea.",
  "page.home.faq.11.question": "HOW DO I GET WHITELISTED?",
  "page.home.faq.11.answer": "You can sign up for the community whitelist on the Kun Agüero and Kuniverse Discord channels. If you own previous The Sandbox Avatar Collections or LAND, you will be able to access a priority whitelist.",
  "page.home.faq.12.question": "HOW DO I KNOW IF IM WHITELISTED?",
  "page.home.faq.12.answer": "If you own The Sandbox LAND or previous Avatar Collections, or if you've registered your wallet in the Kuniverse Whitelist Discord channel, you're automatically whitelisted in the second wave. During this period, you will be able to mint by connecting your wallet to the minting page",
  "page.home.faq.13.question": "MY AVATARS ARE NOT REVEALED YET ON OPENSEA, WHAT CAN I DO?",
  "page.home.faq.13.answer": "The avatars will be revealed on November 4th, 2022. If you are checking before they have been revealed, this is normal. If you are checking after that date, press the “Refresh Metadata” button on the top-right corner of OpenSea.",
  "page.home.faq.14.question": "BUYING NFT FOR THE FIRST TIME, HOW CAN I GET STARTED?",
  "page.home.faq.14.answer": "<p>The process is quite simple. You need to ensure that you have:</p> <ul class=\"list-disc\"> <li>Created a compatible wallet to mint your avatar </li> <li>Ensure you have both the correct amount of SAND to mint the number of avatars you want and some ETH to cover the gas fees.</li> <li>Log into your account and head over to the mint page: <a href=\"https://kuniverse.sandbox.game\">https://kuniverse.sandbox.game</a></li> <li>Check that your wallet is properly connected and just press the MINT YOUR AVATAR button to retrieve your Avatar.</li> </ul>",
  "page.home.brands.title": "Brands & IPs alreadyin The Sandbox Metaverse.",
  "page.home.brands.participation": "In participation with",
  "page.connect.wallet.signin": "Sing in..",
  "page.connect.wallet.is.beeing.verify.title": "WALLET IS BEING VERIFIED",
  "page.connect.wallet.is.beeing.verify.text": "Please wait while you are redirected",
  "general.error.title": "SOMETHING WENT WRONG",
  "general.error.text": "The Application has encountered an unknown error",
  "page.connect.wallet.connect": "CONNECT YOUR WALLET",
  "page.connect.wallet.disclaimer": "We recommend the use of WalletConnect for mobile experience",
  "page.mint.nft.wait.prepare": "Wait until we prepare your wallet...",
  "page.mint.nft.transaction": "Your transaction is being processed.",
  "page.mint.nft.success.title": "Successfully minted your NFT!",
  "page.mint.nft.success.text": "Please wait while you are redirected",
  "page.mint.nft.not.whitelisted.title": "NOT WHITELISTED",
  "page.mint.nft.not.whitelisted.text": "Your connected wallet is not in the welcome list. Make sure to be connected with the correct wallet.",
  "page.mint.nft.not.whitelisted.button": "Reconnect",
  "page.connect.wallet.try.again": "Try again",
  "page.mint.nft.not.available.title": "NOT AVAILABLE",
  "page.mint.nft.not.available.text": "Your connected wallet is not allowed to mint more avatars.",
  "page.mint.nft.connected": "YOUR WALLET IS CONNECTED!",
  "page.mint.nft.connected.how.many": "How many avatars do you want?",
  "page.mint.nft.connected.info.label": "To mint your avatar you need SAND on the Ethereum network",
  "page.mint.nft.mint.now": "Mint Now",
  "page.my.avatars.title": "My Avatars",
  "page.my.avatars.loading": "Loading...",
  "page.mint.buy.sand": "BUY SAND",
  "page.mint.loading.price": "Loading price...",
  "page.mint.nft.not.enough.sand.founds": "Not enough SAND founds"
}
